(electric guitar plays
mellow rock intro)
♪ I hopped off the plane
at LAX ♪
♪ With a dream and my cardigan ♪
♪ Welcome to land of fame,
excess ♪
♪ Whoa! Am I gonna fit in? ♪
♪ Jumped in a cab,
here I am for the first time ♪
♪ Look to my right
and I see the Hollywood sign ♪
♪ This is all so crazy ♪
♪ Everybody seems so famous ♪
♪ My tummy's turning,
and I'm feeling kinda homesick ♪
♪ Too much pressure
and I'm nervous ♪
♪ That's when the taximan
turned on the radio ♪
♪ And a Jay-Z song was on ♪
♪ And a Jay-Z song
was on ♪
♪ And a Jay-Z song was on ♪
♪ So I put my hands up,
they're playing my song ♪
♪ The butterflies fly away ♪
♪ Nodding my head like, yeah ♪
♪ Moving my hips like, yeah ♪
♪ I got my hands up,
they're playing my song ♪
♪ I know I'm gonna be okay ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ It's a party in the USA ♪
♪ Get to the club
in my taxicab ♪
♪ Everybody's
looking at me now ♪
♪ Like who's that chick
that's rockin' kicks ♪
♪ Gotta be from outta town ♪
♪ So hard with my girls
not around me ♪
♪ It's definitely
not a Nashville party ♪
♪ 'Cause all I see
are stilettos ♪
♪ I guess I never got the memo ♪
♪ My tummy's turning,
and I'm feeling kinda homesick ♪
♪ Too much pressure
and I'm nervous ♪
♪ That's when the DJ dropped
my favorite tune ♪
♪ And a Britney song was on ♪
♪ And a Britney song
was on ♪
♪ And a Britney song was on ♪
♪ So I put my hands up,
they're playing my song ♪
♪ The butterflies fly away ♪
♪ Nodding my head like, yeah ♪
♪ Moving my hips like, yeah ♪
♪ I got my hands up,
they're playing my song ♪
♪ I know I'm gonna be okay ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ It's a party in the USA ♪
♪ Felt like hopping on
a flight ♪
♪ On a flight ♪
♪ Back to my hometown tonight ♪
♪ Hometown tonight ♪
♪ Something stops me
every time ♪
♪ Every time ♪
♪ The DJ plays my song
and I feel all right ♪
♪ So I put my hands up,
they're playing my song ♪
♪ The butterflies fly away ♪
♪ Nodding my head like, yeah ♪
♪ Nodding my head ♪
♪ Moving my hips like, yeah ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I got my hands up,
they're playing my song ♪
♪ I know I'm gonna be okay ♪
♪ Gonna be okay ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ It's a party in the USA ♪
♪ So I put my hands up,
they're playing my song ♪
♪ The butterflies fly away ♪
♪ Fly way ♪
♪ Nodding my head like, yeah ♪
♪ Nodding my head ♪
♪ Moving my hips like, yeah ♪
♪ I got my hands up,
they're playing my song ♪
♪ I know I'm gonna be okay ♪
♪ I'm gonna be okay ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ It's a party in the USA ♪
♪ It's a party in the USA! ♪